♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
[Christine] How cute is
this space right now?
-[Maya] It's so cute.
-[Christine] Do you love it?
This is perfect.
Our agents have been
so successful this year.
This is our best year ever.
Chrishell just closed Queens,
and everyone's been kicking ass.
So we wanted to throw
a cocktail party to celebrate.
-Hi!
-Oh, hi!
[Jason] Hey.
[Mary] Mmm, how are you?
-[Jason] Hey, babe.
-[Mary] I'll get you some champagne.
Cheers.
-[Maya] Slow down on the champagne!
-[cheering]
-Mike.
-Maya. Nice to meet you.
[Mike] Maya, nice meeting you.
[Jason] Brett's wasted, so...
-Who's this?
-This is Alex.
Finally I meet you! Hi. I'm Heather.
Nice to meet you.
See, her boyfriend exists.
Your boyfriend--
-Well, my boyfriend--
-Where is your imaginary boyfriend?
My girlfriend's not here, so...
[Heather] You don't have a girlfriend.
Oh.
-[Maya] That is good.
-Exactly.
I'd rather have a man that's working
than a man that's sitting around
doing nothing, right?
-He's a professional athlete.
-Exactly. And he's hot.
[woman] Boo-ya!
Oh, I want to tell you, like, good job
on Queens. Cheers, girl.
-Thank you.
-We just closed Queens.
Yeah, I know. That's awesome.
-Yay!
-I mean, beginner's luck, but you know...
-[Maya] Come on!
-There was a lot of work involved.
First rodeo!
It's not my first or second or third,
but it is my biggest, so...
-[Maya] Good job on that one.
-Thank you.
Yeah.
And hopefully your client is happy, and--
Davina is very supportive of you.
Is everything okay between you guys?
[mouths] I don't know.
I don't think Davina has it out for me.
I just think it's one of those things
where when you do something well,
she's thinking in her head,
"That should've been me."
So it's hard for her
to be happy for other people,
but you don't have to be a dick.
Can I say that? [chuckles]
You don't have to be a dick about it.
[chuckles]
♪ Come to life ♪
♪ Well, if you don't like girls
That are stronger than you ♪
That are smarter than you ♪
♪ Well, then you might not like me ♪
♪ Might not like me... ♪
-Watch Monday night football, Mary?
-No.
Monday night football's the Raiders.
You will watch Monday night football.
-Are they good this year?
-Don't know.
-No one knows. It's the first game.
-Oh.
Well, don't they do pre-season?
Or is this pre-season?
We were good in pre-season,
but that doesn't mean shit.
That's like looking good
in your Tinder profile, but then--
-Monday is the date.
-[Mary chuckles]
-That's actually a really good analogy.
-Analogy?
[Brett] You're welcome for that one.
Morning!
-[Jason] Hey, what's up, Doug?
-How are you doing?
Good to see you, man.
-Can we talk?
-Yeah, sure.
-Coffee?
-[Doug] Coffee would be great.
-And I'm kind of in a hurry, but--
-Yeah? We'll be fine.
So what's happening?
My house is not happening.
-Yeah, hasn't sold yet.
-[chuckles]
Are you coming here to tell me
you're ready to reduce the price?
Or get rid of my realtor.
-I'm kidding.
-[chuckles]
Um, we can talk about that.
[Jason] Doug is a great client.
We've done three or four deals,
and all of them have been significant.
So I'd say north of $20 million for sure.
And we've known him
and represented him for years.
He's certainly one
of our most important clients.
You need your housekeeper
to dust these, uh...
-Do I?
-Yeah!
-This place gets cleaned like, every--
-It's terrible.
Okay.
Six months.
No offers, not even one.
[Jason] Well, we're also listed high.
[Doug] We're also in Trousdale Estates.
My blood's up to here right now. Sorry.
It's frustrating. The house has been on
longer than both of us anticipated.
But it doesn't have city views.
It's no fault of yours.
It just doesn't have city views.
And that's what people are paying
that type of money for
if you're trying to get
over $2,000 a square foot.
We also think
the house should be listed...
under ten.
So, what's Christine doing?
How many showings has she had?
Do you know?
About a dozen.
Most of those occurred when we were
closer to coming on the market.
Obviously, you're going to get a rush of
activity, you know, the first few weeks,
but a home that's valued
at over $10 million
doesn't get a phone call every day.
If I reduce to nine-nine-five,
I want it sold.
I think with a new price
we're gonna get a lot of activity.
-Three months.
-I'll say that.
I would not be surprised if we could
not get an offer
within the first three months.
-Especially at that price.
-Good.
-All right, man. Done.
-Hey, how are you?
Your client Doug is upstairs.
Oh, Doug's here?
-Yep.
-Oh, okay.
-Head up there.
-Okay.
-Thanks, Doug.
-Thank you.
-Thanks so much.
-Yeah.
Hi, Doug.
When a client stops in unexpectedly,
usually it means that they're frustrated.
And it's not a good sign.
Good to see you.
I talked to Jason.
We're reducing the price.
-You've got three months.
-Okay. Thank you.
Why don't we go over
what Doug and I just talked about?
You guys should clean this stuff up here.
-See you later. Take care.
-See you.
Doug is going to reduce the price
to nine-nine-nine-five.
That's a significant reduction.
Hopefully, we can still salvage this.
Hopefully, we can still breathe
some life into this listing,
even though it's been
on the market for so long.
And I think making sure that everyone
that already knows about that house
now knows that we just did
a $2 million reduction,
-that's almost a 20% reduction.
-Yeah.
It's gonna reflect on you
if we can't get him an offer.
Well, I'm on it.
I have tons of people I can call,
and I'll get started on it right now.
I'll prove to him
-that I was the right person to work with.
-That's all I wanna hear. Thank you.
♪ Moving your body
The rhythm, your soul ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
Hello, baby.
-Hey.
-How are you?
Good. How are you?
Good.
-So how's work?
-This morning? It's good.
I'm trying to negotiate this deal
for one of my clients.
She wants to come in really low
on an offer, and--
-Hello, how are we doing today?
-Hi.
Can I get you anything to drink?
A coffee for me, a latte.
-Coff-- A latte?
-I'm gonna do a chai tea latte
-with almond milk.
-Sounds good.
-Thank you.
-What are you looking at?
-Wedding stuff.
[Romain] Mm-hmm.
I've got them all organized. Dresses...
Uh... destinations,
themes...
All right, so...
If we want to go to Bali,
like where we could be right on the water.
[Romain] Mm-hmm.
-Yeah, that's nice.
-I know.
-Here we are.
-[both] Oh, thank you.
My pleasure.
I've got the almond chai tea latte.
And for you, sir,
I've got the whole milk latte.
-[Mary] Thanks.
-[Romain] Thank you.
So what do you think between places?
There's Bali. We could do something
a little bit closer.
-Whatever you prefer. I mean...
-So you don't care...
what... even what destination we go to?
Any of those places would be fine for me.
-It's more the one you're gonna choose.
-Okay.
All right, so, then...
this is what I was thinking.
I think this is so pretty.
I love this dress.
Do you like that?
-Yeah.
-You seem, like, bored by this.
No, I mean... It's more...
It's a girl thing.
-But it's your wedding!
-Yeah, but it's a girl thing.
You know, dress, flower... I mean...
I like it, but it's more something
you should, I mean, know.
I ain't gonna ask Jason or Brett
which flower I should get? You know?
Jason picks out
all the stuff in his house.
But it's a decoration for a house.
Yeah, decoration for...
And this is a decoration for our wedding.
Yeah, but it's girl stuff.
A wedding, babe.
I mean... You know what I mean?
I would like you to be interested.
I never say I wasn't.
I would prefer you to choose.
So, I'll just pick,
like, neon purple and blue
and stuff like that to go at the wedding.
You're cool with that?
I mean, if that's what you want...
You're being annoying.
I'm not annoying, babe. I just--
But I get excited about it. You're not.
Yes, I am.
I'm just saying that you should--
You're the one that asked me
to marry you, and--
It doesn't mean that I need
to plan the wedding.
Maybe until you're ready
to help plan the wedding,
-maybe we shouldn't get married.
-Why?
Do you even want to still get married?
-Yes, I do!
-Or you just don't want to plan a wedding?
No, I just...
I just don't think it should be me
planning the wedding.
So you think it should just be me?
As busy as I am, you think I should
just add this onto my plate, too?
No, I'm not saying that. I'm just saying
it's a girl thing and then...
Fine.
Hi, this is Christine Quinn
at the Oppenheim Group.
So, listen, I'm calling in regards
to my property
that you actually viewed in Beverly Hills.
We just had a $2 million price reduction
and I wanted to see if you were interested
in getting back out there to see it.
[man] Oh, well, thank you so much.
Unfortunately, it's still out of our price
range, even with the reduced price.
All right. Thank you so much
for your time. I really appreciate it.
[groans]
[Maya] He said no bueno?
-It's still out of his price point.
-What?
I saw his financials,
I mean, he could afford it.
I just think
that he was going through a job change,
-and I don't really think he felt stable.
-Okay.
Well, it's like my client can afford
Harold and he ended up leasing it.
And now I have to deal
with being a property manager.
Maya, I can see you being
a real Israeli slum lord.
[laughs]
[in Israeli accent]
You are late on your rent!
Exactly.
I would like to have her as a landlord.
You know, I feel like she'd probably yell
at me for my rent being late all the time,
but then she'd laugh and laugh
and be like, "Want to grab margaritas?"
And I'd be like, "Yeah, let's go."
[line ringing]
This is Lindsay.
Hi, Lindsay, how are you? This is
Christine Quinn with the Oppenheim Group.
Hi, Christine.
[line ringing]
-[woman] Hello.
-Emily?
Yes, Emily speaking.
Hi, this is Christine Quinn
with the Oppenheim Group. How are you?
Listen, I'm calling because you viewed
my property in Beverly Hills
and we had a significant price reduction.
Listen, you had emailed me a while back
about some clients
that you had interested in my...
I'm good, thank you. Listen, I'm calling
in regards to my property
in Trousdale Estates...
[woman] Yeah, I already sold them
a property in Trousdale Estates.
Unfortunately, I actually think
that we are no longer in the market.
All right, thank you so much.
I appreciate it. Have a good day.
-[woman] I'm sorry.
-No, that's okay. Congratulations.
I hope New York is amazing.
-Thank you so much.
-Okay. Take care.
-Have a lovely day.
-You, too. Bye, Sarah.
[groans]
♪ I can feel it sinking in ♪
♪ The silhouette, silhouette
Stands from the truth again ♪
♪ Are we gonna sink or swim? ♪
♪ He got me once, fooled me twice
Won't see you there again ♪
Every time I'm here, it looks like
it's moving a little closer to the end.
I want it dialed in to the point
where if somebody closes escrow,
they can walk into this house,
there's cars in the garage,
there's staff working in the house,
and they're ready to go from day one.
[Jason] I couldn't agree more. Perfect.
So they can come in
-and buy this fully furnished?
-Right.
-Hi, guys.
-Hey, how's it going?
How are you? I'm solo.
You're mad at me?
-Hi, I'm Heather.
-Hi. Jeff.
-Nice to meet you.
-I was expecting Brandon.
I know. I'm so sorry. He couldn't make it.
He's working. He works for one of the
largest architecture firms in the world.
So he couldn't come out,
but he's coming next weekend.
Jeff and I have
a very long-standing close relationship,
but it certainly doesn't
make me look good,
that I tell him there's a client
showing up and he doesn't show up.
Tell me about the, uh, client of yours.
One of my friends,
it's his client and his investor.
Um, he lives in China.
And we are casually having dinner
and I brought up this home.
And he has a Chinese investor
that really wants to move to LA.
He wants this whole Hollywood lifestyle.
So I brought Brandon here
and he loves it.
And now the renderings, I think,
are selling it even more, so I'm excited.
[chuckles]
Heather knows how busy I am,
and she should understand
that anybody selling
a 40-plus-million-dollar house
is probably busy as well.
Doesn't look good for me
or for the Oppenheim Group.
Doesn't look good for Heather.
It's not something that I think
should happen really, ever.
I know, I'm sorry. Um...
I know your schedule's busy, so...
We'll get Brandon here.
I want you to meet him at some point.
-And thank you.
-All right, bud.
-Good to see you.
-Same here. Take care.
-I'll catch up with you.
-[Heather] Thank you.
[engine starts]
I have to say, I'm a little disappointed
that Brandon didn't make it
and, more importantly,
that you didn't tell me.
So I didn't look, you know, stupid
when you just showed up by yourself.
Yeah, I was literally, like,
on the phone with him.
"I need you here. I don't want
to cancel this meeting. It's huge."
I didn't want to cancel.
-I thought that would look worse.
-That would be worse.
Obviously, I mean,
I'm glad that you showed up.
My concern is, one, him not showing up.
Two, I haven't met his client.
I haven't seen proof of funds.
I don't know that much about his client.
You know, I will try to get that.
Because I also want to know,
so I don't look stupid.
I just always like to be over-prepared.
I like to have the answer to every
question before I go into any situation.
I think working with you,
you've taught me that
-and I need to be better about that.
-I don't need you to just be prepared.
I need you to be overly prepared
all the time.
Okay.
This is a huge listing for him,
so he has to be careful. I get that.
But like I said to him,
"You met Brandon. You trust Brandon."
I'm an asset to Oppenheim Group
and I think they need to realize that
'cause I could walk out this door any day
and I've been thinking that I might go
move and live with Nick in Sweden.
Is there anything else that I need to do
that I'm not doing then?
Just be overly prepared all the time.
Okay.
♪ Trying to be the big bad boy ♪
♪ But everything you say is noise
I'm telling you ♪
♪ Kind of funny how it last played out ♪
♪ People tell me, "Wow!"
So what you saying now? ♪
-♪ You tell me that you grew up ♪
-♪ Please ♪
♪ Why you keep on bugging me?
I'm worndering ♪
♪ Did you learn nothing? ♪
[woman] Do you guys want
anything  to drink? Champagne, mimosas?
I'm going to do a mimosa, please.
These pants are just...
I've never sat in them.
So I'm like, "Is this
what it feels like to sit in couture?"
-I don't know. Jesus!
-[chuckles]
This was a mistake for a nail salon.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-[Christine] Thanks so much.
-Cheers.
Cheers, babe. Cheers!
-[Christine] How are you and Romain doing?
-We've been working so much.
Like, you know how it
goes up and down a little bit sometimes.
Because we would work so much,
we only see each other,
-like, an hour or two at a time.
-Yeah.
So it kind of feels, at times,
like we are almost,
like, living two separate lives.
We just need a little bit of time
so we can... [chuckles]
-...plan our future, you know?
-Yeah.
Right now, we are just
living in the present, I guess.
[Mary] But I just think that...
that Romain is getting cold feet, maybe.
I am kind of hesitant to tell Christine
because we've gotten into
arguments about this.
She thinks we're rushing.
Uh, she doesn't know if he's ready.
[Christine] I feel like it's really fast.
-And I just want to make sure--
-What, me and Romain?
You and Romain getting engaged.
I wish I could just be
open and honest with her
and not have to hear,
you know, I told you so, but...
She would say it... for sure.
Is everything okay?
Like, with you in general?
It just seems seems like there's a bunch
of things that have been happening lately.
Yeah, I mean, everything's okay.
I just feel like...
everything's happening all at once,
you know?
Yeah.
It's, like, my last intention
is to, like, let people down
or make them think that, you know,
I'm not capable of doing my job.
Honestly, I don't even know myself
what it is, but...
It kind of seems like
since the new girls have come, you just--
you haven't quite seemed yourself.
Maybe I have been off my game.
Yeah. I don't know.
Like, we were all doing so amazing before,
kicking ass and taking names.
And I just feel like they came and it
just started, like, a whirlwind of drama.
-Right.
-And I've been focusing on that.
And it's been irritating. I just feel like
that's been kind of snowballing things.
Don't let the new girls, like, get to you.
I mean, you know who you are.
You're Christine.
Everyone's scared of you.
-Right!
-I mean, show them that.
-I know, I need to keep it that way.
-I know. Remind them!
-I know, you're right.
-[laughs]
♪ Give me one reason
Let me light this fuse ♪
♪ Tie me up... ♪
-[Brett] Yo!
-[Jason] What's up, bud?
Hey, man.
Looks like you took care of everything.
Good job.
I'm so excited to see this
because I haven't seen it since...
we came here
when it was under construction.
It really looks nice. You pulled it off.
[Jason] Thanks, man.
[Christine] Wow!
It's Buster + Punch. It's the same brand,
that bracelet that I always wear.
-Oh, I love it!
-That looks like this?
Is Mary gonna do the tour?
-[laughs] Hi!
-Hi, hon.
-Looks so good in here!
-Beautiful!
-Hi, babe.
-Hey, honey.
-It looks amazing.
-So incredible.
[Mary] My love!
[Heather] Ooh, it looks pretty.
-The house looks so nice.
-Cute.
Wow! Yeah, that's pretty.
-[Brett] What's up, guys?
-[Chrishell] What's up?
-Hi, guys.
-Wow, this is great!
Hey, ladies.
-This is amazing.
-Hi.
-How are you?
[Maya] So Jason owns
a few houses up in the hills.
He rents them, usually.
And he did an amazing job.
Every new house that he does, he does
even a better job than the previous house.
But I don't think he can commit
to a house long term.
I think they can commit
to only one thing: to the dogs.
[Heather] I love the ceilings.
-[Jason] Library.
-[Heather] Wow!
[Heather] It's so different
than I thought you would do.
[Jason] Yeah, it's very timeless.
-Did you design the whole thing?
-[Jason] Yeah.
Oh, I want to show you this.
This is really cool.
-Boom!
-[Christine] Oh, my God.
[Jason] You will never see
an 85-inch TV...
come out of the ground.
-You ladies ever seen something like this?
-[chuckles]
Just say yes to make him mad, please.
Just say, "Yeah."
[Jason] Pop it.
[all cheer]
Here's to family, guys.
[Maya] Shit. What is this? Shit!
Brett, seriously?
Are we at, like,
a child's party or something?
What is going on? Champagne spraying?
That's so trashy.
Uh, what you're wearing is not, though.
[chuckles]
Oh, my God!
[Heather] Oh! [screams]
[screams]
No!
Hey!
-[Heather gasps] Oh!
-Shit!
I need some more pink rosé.
I'll join you over here in the shade.
Did you put your feet in the water yet?
So when are you guys gonna get married?
-What do you think? You have a date?
-[Mary] Next year.
Um, we need to find
the right place and, um...
[Maya] That's exciting.
-Yeah.
-[Maya] He sounds very excited!
-He doesn't seem interested.
-No, I just feel like it's a girl thing.
-[Maya chuckles]
-I mean...
But two people are getting married.
[chuckles]
A guy and a girl, right?
So it is a girl thing.
-He's not helping much.
-You're just gonna show up, huh?
-Like...
-No.
Chrishell, did your husband help you
plan the wedding?
-Did he what?
-Help you plan the wedding.
He did.
I was surprised. There were things
I thought I was gonna just do.
[Mary] See? Talk to Justin.
[Chrishell] And he actually was like,
"What about this?"
And I was like, "Oh, okay."
-See? Tell him it's not just a girl thing.
-[Maya] You're in a tight spot, Romain.
[Jason] If I could gather everyone...
[Maya] Can you do it fast?
My nipples are getting hard.
Maya's nipples are getting hard,
I'll be quick.
[Maya] I'm getting cold.
All of us got a cute gift for Maya,
so I wanna give it to you.
-Oh, wow. Thank you, guys.
-[all] Aw.
-Little baby outfits!
-[Maya] Oh, my gosh.
[all] Aw!
-[Maya] This is so cute!
-[Heather] How cute!
-This is so cute.
-[Chrishell] That is so cute.
[Maya] My God. I love it.
The newest member.
It's never too early to start branding.
[Maya] Covers my boobs, so that's good.
Yeah, he's gonna be
a good little door knocker. I can tell.
[Maya] I know, right?
She!
I don't know.  Well, speaking of,
I have a little surprise for you, too.
-Twins?
-No, I wish, actually.
-No, you don't.
-I kind of do. Well, not...
Not if they are like you!
[Maya chuckles]
So I actually got a cake
for all of you guys.
And it's gonna be a sex--
-Gender reveal.
-Ah!
-Not sex reveal.
We know you had sex, Maya.
We got it.
[all laugh]
-Go get the cake.
-[Jason] Bring the cake out.
I don't get it. How is it gonna say--
It's gonna be pink or blue frosting
on the inside of the cake.
-So if it's blue--
-Don't talk to me!
-Oh, my God!
-[Brett] If it's blue, it's a boy.
-And if it's pink, it's a girl.
-[Maya] You guys ready?
-[all cheer]
-[Brett] Ah, it's a boy!
[all] Yeah!
Whoo!
I like boys.
Nice, Maya!
Mwah!
[Maya] Hopefully,
everything is good and healthy.
I'm looking forward to meet him.
I'm happy. I'm very excited.
I'm thrilled, actually.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-I haven't talked to you all day.
-I know. I haven't talked to you either.
What's going on?
Oh, not much, just excited
for Maya and her baby.
-I know.
-We'll see how that works out.
Um... So, you know, some of the girls
were saying they felt, like,
kind of a little bit of tension
in the office between us. I don't know.
Do you feel like there is tension?
I'm not going to lie. Yes.
-I do feel like there's a little tension.
-Yeah.
Um, I mean, my assumption is
that you just don't like me.
-[chuckles] I don't know.
-Not true. I don't know you.
So, how could I just not like you?
But I feel like,
at the same time, of what I've seen
makes me a little, like, resistant
to trust you, because when you first
joined us and Mary came to the office
and she had the whole, you know,
that dinner with Romain
where they talked about
their future and stuff,
she was crying, you know.
You were so empathetic to her,
which I thought was really sweet.
But then you kind of questioned
their relationship
when you and I were talking.
I felt like you were, though, you know?
You see, that's where
everything's coming from,
because I think
that's so weird that you say that.
We were having a conversation,
a private conversation.
-Yeah.
-And I was asking you questions.
And then you turned it around to Mary
and made it sound like
I was talking bad about her.
And just now you said that I was
and I wasn't. I was asking questions
in a private situation
'cause I didn't know.
-Mm-hmm.
-So...
I was thinking it was a cool vibe
to, like, ask you privately.
But I also feel like the way you asked
was not necessarily neutral.
It was kind of like you had
an opinion about it.
-Okay.
-You were saying she should get a prenup.
I think everybody should get a prenup.
I didn't know that, and you don't know me
either, so it's kind of, like, you know,
lost in translation, maybe. I don't know.
But it seemed
like it wasn't a neutral opinion.
-It seemed like it was opinionated.
-Right.
I don't like two-faced people,
and I'm not saying you are two-faced,
but it's going that direction
and I was like, "Oh, wow,
you were super nice to her,"
but then you didn't actually tell it,
like, you were very supportive to her.
So I was like, "Oh, wow."
Like, at least I'm direct, you know?
Wow! That was a lot. Okay.
Again, at least I'm honest, you know?
I'd rather that than have to guess,
like, where you stand.
Okay, so you think that I'm two-faced?
I didn't say that.
I said I didn't... I'm not saying you are,
but it's going in that direction.
Okay. Well, I will leave it at that.
I don't feel like anything
I have to say past this point
-you're gonna change your opinion.
-That's not true.
It's very clear
that this is going the wrong way.
All right. Well, I'm sorry
that you feel that way and, um...
-What can we do, you know?
-[chuckles]
What can we do? Okay.
It's almost impossible
to be friends with Davina.
At this point, my hands are...
I just give up.
And I see who she is
and I'm just going to do what I can
to work with her in a cordial way.
But I now know that there's no mistaking.
We're not friends.
What's going on?
We just had a little conversation
about the vibe in the office.
Where's my purse?
[Christina] What's going on?
-The weird vibe between you guys?
-Um, I mean...
Yeah, a little bit. Something like that.
-Is my purse by you, Heather?
-Uh... Yes.
Are you leaving?
-Yeah, I'm gonna go.
-You are?
Yeah.
[Davina] Unnecessarily dramatic.
I'm just gonna go inside for one second.
See you guys in a second.
[Davina] I know, so dramatic!
I just feel like
there was a weird vibe in the office...
'Cause Chrishell is fake?
I mean... [chuckles] Kind of, you know?
-What do you mean?
-Yeah!
I told her. I basically said she's going
down the path of being two-faced.
-I agree.
-It makes me not trust her.
It's like you say things
and then you don't own up to them.
Like, the dinner that we had,
when I asked Chrishell what she said
and she wouldn't own up to it.
"You were that blacked out
you don't remember what you said?"
I'm not the only person that sees it.
Know what I mean?
Come on, no. Honestly.
What happened?
I don't know, just...
Agh, I'm stressed out.
Davina just, like, went in on me.
Honestly, I'm still so, like, thrown off
by what just happened
that it takes me a second to even, like--
-I figured you guys had, like, tension--
-Now she's talking about me to everyone.
Now, like, everyone's gonna hate me.
I didn't even do anything.
She was very surprised that I called her
that she was going down
the two-faced kind of road.
Yeah, I told her. I was like,
"Davina's... straightforward,"
and that's what I told her.
At the end, she kind of, like,
called me two-faced
and I said that... I'm like, "What?"
And she says,
"I'm not saying you're two-faced.
It's going that way."
"I'm not saying you're two-faced,
but you're two-faced?"
She said,
"I'm saying it's going that way."
So I just kind of like...
Davina is very direct.
I just felt like I couldn't keep going
back and forth with her,
so I just, like, left.
Now she's over there talking about me.
Can you come with me over there?
-I feel like I wanna defend myself.
-I'll come with you.
I don't want her talking about me
to everyone.
Why don't you just put it already to rest?
-Like, it's been--
-Yeah, it's so annoying.
Yeah, it was interesting. So I was like,
at least I am more direct, you know?
They're coming.
No, I totally agree.
-Hi, ladies.
-[all] Hi.
Hi, guys.
-Okay, guys.
-What's wrong?
-Davina.
-Yes?
The tension.
What's going on with the tension?
In an open setting, this is super awkward,
I'm just gonna say.
Mary and Romain, I never want
anything but the best for you guys,
and this is dating back a long time ago
where I was basically just asking
because everyone was so concerned
and I don't know the dynamics.
I was asking... I was, like,
in a private scenario with Davina,
I was asking her questions so that I could
know where the concerns were coming from.
I never expected that to come back to you
in a way where it was like I was talking
about you. I was asking questions.
-[Mary] Right.
-And so...
Apparently, you thought
that was me being two-faced.
Which is what I assumed,
because you didn't know,
and I would think
that people could have questions.
[Chrishell]
I wasn't trying to be two-faced.
I was asking questions
in a private setting.
I know you said
"I'm not calling you that."
I didn't feel like
they were neutral questions
I feel like they had, like, an opinion.
They were coming from an opinion.
Does Romain pay
for his own share of stuff, do you think?
-Not much, I think.
-So she pays for everything?
Yeah, I mean...
I don't know him super well.
-I heard he's a baker.
-Yeah.
She's going to do a prenup, right?
Right, but I don't know them,
so I don't have an opinion.
I was asking questions
so that I could form one.
I understand where you're coming from
because she's asked questions.
Even at our dinner,
you asked about Jason and Mary
and that dynamic.
And you don't know anyone
like we all know each other.
You know, it's like a family.
She's new to the family.
I'm totally open to, like, letting it go,
and talking to you guys about it,
-but I still feel--
-Done. What about you, Chrishell?
I still feel like that's my real opinion,
you know?
I'm dying to drop it.
I don't want this, but I don't...
Like, I feel like the talk we just had
privately escalated the whole situation,
'cause then it went to name calling, so...
-It really, like, made things worse...
-I don't know about name calling.
-Yeah, you called me two-faced.
-No, I said it's going down that path.
And it's a question mark.
Chrishell doesn't have a bad bone
in her body. And neither do you.
I don't really know what's going on,
but you guys need to hug it out.
Hold on.
Because all I know
is we were at the happy hour
and I asked what the situation was about.
And I asked you,
you said, "I don't remember."
I said, "What did you guys talk about?
I'm so confused."
You said, "I don't know. I made
some comments about Mary and Romain."
-People are talking.
-I swear to God.
I don't remember.
And you act like you didn't remember
what you talked about.
but then Davina told me in private
that you made some comments about Romain,
and I was like, "Oh, shit.That's so
interesting that all of a sudden,
you know, that came out."
So I feel like you don't own up
to the things that you say
and that's where this is coming from.
Christine, when I had spoken to you,
I was literally racking my brain of,
like, what is she bringing up
that I don't even remember?
I always remember what I say.
I'm like,
"Listen. I said this. I'm sorry." Like...
If I can-- Since we're all talking
about me right now,
sometimes people
are just saying things, doing things.
Your intentions are what matters.
Okay, Mary, if you're questioning that,
I get that--
[Mary] If you're asking questions,
it's your intention.
Own up to what you say. Do you have...
dementia? I don't know.
Own up to what you say.
That's where I'm coming from.
Christine, I think
you're being rough a little bit.
You look like you need
a little hug right now.
I don't... I think that you did...
Like, I don't think that you had
any bad intentions.
The next time I get in a fight with you,
I'll just not remember what happened.
-How about that?
-[Brett] Fine. I'll hug you.
I'll be like, "I don't remember,
I'm not responsible.
Everyone's gonna give me a... hug."
-Ridiculous.
-[Mary] Talk to me.
[Christine] Ridiculous. Please.
-[Brett] Davina.
-I was just asking questions.
Guys, come on.
I have no problem with Chrishell.
-Okay.
-[Brett] Just saying.
All right. Okay, good.
-You did two seconds ago.
-[Christine] You guys are ridiculous.
I wanna drop it if you want to drop it.
[Christine]
Pretend we don't remember things we say?
-[Davina] She's crying?
-I know.
-You know I love you.
-Are you making fun of me?
No, I'm not making fun of you.
I'm just saying it's--
[Christine] This is ridiculous. Come on!
-Christine--
-[Brett] Guys, tone this down.
-[Christine] I'm not trying to be mean.
-[Mary] This is intense.
I'm sorry. I'm not a kiss ass.
I'm not a pushover.
-I'm not fake. I'm just not.
-[Davina] This is crazy.
[Christine] Only my tits are fake.
I'm not.
-[Christine] Sorry.
-I don't...
I'm trying... I don't want to talk to her.
I don't want to cry.
-You're so mean!
-No, I'm not mean.
That bitch is a... liar.
Own up to what you say.
Honestly, it's bullshit.
I'm good friends with her,
but I don't stand for that shit.
-It's just too much.
-[Brett] Honey.
-Don't take it that seriously.
-No, stay.
-Seriously.
-[Maya] Chrishell?
-[Brett] Don't take it seriously.
-[Chrishell] I don't want them to think--
-[Maya] Are you okay?
-[Chrishell] It's too much.
-[Brett] It was way too much.
-[Chrishell] It was traumatic.
-Honestly. Like, how pathetic is she?
-Unnecessarily dramatic.
So pathetic.
[Maya] Chrishell, come here for a sec.
I don't want you to be hurt by Christine.
Christine was a bit rough.
Crazy night.
Wow!
At the end of the day, I feel like
at that dinner, you conveniently--
[Brett] This isn't about making points.
-Can you stop? I'm... trying to--
-I know, but you made your point.
-Trust me.
-Can I reiterate and you get off my back?
I always own up to my stuff.
If, in the moment, I didn't know exactly
what she was talking about,
now I've already talked to Mary.
I've told her everything I said.
I own up to everything I've said.
I understand that, but we came back
from the bathroom, Maya and I,
and we had asked you
what you guys were talking about.
You said "I don't remember. I just said
stuff about Mary and Romain."
Christine, I'm not having
this conversation with you.
-Because you know that I'm right.
-Christine, here's the thing.
You said you don't remember.
-It makes you sound like you're two-faced.
-Also, I don't have to tell you
-what I said if I don't feel...
-Also, it makes you sound two-faced
when you don't own up
to the shit that you say.
Do you understand where I'm coming from?
-When I ask you what did you say--
-Don't yell at me.
-When I ask you...
-Hold on. Take it down.
-...what did you say, and you don't own up
to what you said,
it makes you look like a crazy person.
If you keep yelling at me,
I'm not gonna listen to you.
I always own up to what I say.
I said, "I said this. So what?
I said this. I'll back it up."
Christine, I've talked to Mary
about what I said.
But when I asked you at the dinner,
you conveniently didn't remember.
You understand the difference, right?
Or do you still have dementia?
Christine.
-Leave everything behind.
-I mean, come on.
Yeah, no rebuttal because I'm right.
Christine, this is enough.
-I mean, seriously?
-I'm leaving. Don't do this again to me.
♪ Get out of my way ♪
♪ I'm not afraid
I'm not afraid ♪
Seriously, that bitch should...
own a Sunglass Hut
-'cause she's so... shady.
-Really?
[Christine] Yeah! She's so... shady.
I was protecting you as my best friend.
[Mary] I appreciate that.
You're not good in my book
when you talk shit about my friends.
But I... All right.
♪ My true colors
I'll show you, I'll show you ♪
♪ Ain't supposed to not cover ♪
♪ I'll show you
I'll show you the way... ♪
[Chrishell] Hi.
Chrishell.
Thank you.
♪ I'll show you my true colors ♪
♪ I'll show you
I'll show you ♪
[Maya] Thank you.
We just wanted to show you something.
If you'll look up...
Oh, my God!
-Oh, wow!
-Oh, my God!
-It's amazing!
-That is amazing.
-Nice job.
-Awesome.
[Jason] It's a great photo.
-It looks so good! Oh, my God!
-So good.
This is so great.
Thank you for such a great year.
You guys certainly earned this.
I think it's cool to see yourself
in Sunset Plaza. It's the main strip.
And you see all these big billboards
for, like, big TV shows
and all that stuff,
and all of a sudden, us up there.
I appreciate that he chose to spend
his money not just on book collections,
but also on, like, a billboard for us.
Look at us, guys.
-We made it!
-[Brett] You made it!
Wait, where is Chrishell?
Yeah, where is Chrishell?
I don't know.
Hopefully, she'll show up. Yeah.
Well, has anyone talked to her today?
No?
Did you get a chance
to talk to her after...
No, I mean, she blocked me.
I tried to apologize after the party
and she blocked me.
And then blocked me on Instagram.
So I had no way of apologizing.
-All right.
-At the end of the day,
I tried to call her because
I did want to apologize for my delivery.
And I know that I was drinking
and things were heated.
I think she was blindsided by it.
She's not used to you
or the family environment so much.
-I think so, too.
-Yeah.
But in fairness,
I'm newer to the group, too, you know,
and I'm a little more direct as well,
and so I had a similar conversation with
her, but it was just more calm, you know.
-'Cause you're mature.
-I wasn't, you know, so drunk, either.
-[Jason] There she is.
-Hi.
Hi, guys.
Hi, how are you?
We were wondering where you were.
-I'm here.
-Wait. Did you see this?
I couldn't miss such a big moment.
Oh, my gosh!
Congratulations! That's so cool.
That's amazing. Congrats, everybody.
That looks so good.
Everyone looks awesome.
Thank you.
-Hi.
I'd love to give you a hug,
but you don't have to.
Hi, how are you?
[Christine] I'd love to give you a hug.
And, you know, just to let you know,
I did try to call you after.
Chrishell, I'm talking to you.
I did try to call you after
and apologize about my delivery.
I know it was extremely strong.
-I tried to apologize.
-I have nothing to speak to you about.
This is about me genuinely apologizing.
-Thank you.
-As I tried to do when it happened,
-but you blocked me.
-I didn't block you.
I've been through a lot in my life
and I think it would take a lot more
than Christine to bully me
out of a good situation
that I worked really hard to get to.
This is a great moment.
We're celebrating a good time.
[Jason] Listen.
Let's remember we're here to--
Like Christine said,
we're here to celebrate.
-[Brett] Yeah.
-I tried.
[Chrishell] I've tackled bigger bullies
than her in the past ,
and this one won't be any different.
♪ We belong at the top ♪
♪ Even all that we've got ♪
♪ No, we ain't gonna stop ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ We're faster, we're stronger than you
Even though we're hotter than fire ♪
♪ We're better than gold ♪
♪ Oh, we belong at the top ♪
♪ We belong at the top ♪
♪ Confidence is dangerous ♪